<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asia on David Calhoun - Photography Blog</title>
    <link>https://davidcalhounphotography.com/blog/categories/asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asia on David Calhoun - Photography Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://davidcalhounphotography.com&#34;&gt;David Calhoun&lt;/a&gt; 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 09:14:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://davidcalhounphotography.com/blog/categories/asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: Travel photography in Japan: part two</title>
      <link>https://davidcalhounphotography.com/blog/video-travel-photography-in-japan-part-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 09:14:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidcalhounphotography.com/blog/video-travel-photography-in-japan-part-two/</guid>
      <description>  Check out the first video here.
A few weeks back I took another trip to Japan, a few days of which were dedicated to taking photos.
In this second video I visit the Arashiyama Bamboo Forest in western Kyoto and the Fushimi Inari Shrine just south of Kyoto city.
Arashiyama Bamboo Forest in Kyoto, Japan  Some general tips from the video:
 for popular locations, book lodging nearby and walk over SUPER early to beat the crowds (you need to walk because public transportation doesn&amp;rsquo;t run 24&amp;frasl;7 in Japan) HDR has legitimate applications when there are extreme exposure differences (bright whites and dark blacks), such as in forests where the light shines through the trees especially for low light situations, bring a tripod and shoot at low ISO if you want a quality print with little noise  Fushimi Inari Shrine torii in Kyoto, Japan  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: Travel photography in Japan (part one)</title>
      <link>https://davidcalhounphotography.com/blog/video-travel-photography-in-japan-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 14:49:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidcalhounphotography.com/blog/video-travel-photography-in-japan-part-one/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks back I took another trip to Japan, a few days of which were dedicated to taking photos. In this first video you can really tell that I got around - I definitely got some good use of the JR Pass, which gives you unlimited access to the bullet trains.
Atomic Bomb Dome from Aioi Bridge (Hiroshima, Japan)  Floating torii: Itsukushima Shrine (Miyajima Shrine) near Hiroshima, Japan  Togetsukyo Bridge in Arashiyama (Kyoto, Japan)  Filming locations in this video:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>